bicyclebluebook.com 2015-11-01

# Privacy Statement - Used Bicycle Value - BicycleBlueBook.com

Bicycle Book, LLC, DBA: Bicycle Blue Book ("we," "our," and "us") believes that trust is the basis for successful communities and successful merchants. We fully understand that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so with a high level of security. We are committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of information that we collect from you. We (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale or exchange with other marketers; (2) honor customers' requests not to share their information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone or other solicitations from us.

##### Collecting Information About You

In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics. There may be times (such as when you subscribe to a service, or to participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) at which we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, etc. Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our web site.

##### Using Information About You

We use the information we collect from you for purposes that will help us serve you better, such as confirming and verifying subscription or registration, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, etc. We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we and our partners offer. We may also use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about us, and to process payments for services. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to our specified purposes. We do not otherwise disclose your information to third-parties.

##### Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Personal Information

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us, please email us at [support@BicycleBlueBook.com](mailto:support@BicycleBlueBook.com), or call customer service at (408) 209-2558 during our normal business hours. Please be sure to include your email address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, street address or other personal information with us please contact us the same way. Please note that sometimes these requests may take up to 6-8 weeks to be effective, particularly if we are removing your name from postal mailings. In addition, when you subscribe to our services, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions, even if you have opted to not receive communications. We also reserve the right to contact you in the event of extenuating circumstances.

##### Security

We use encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of your personal information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web site, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will do our best to protect its security on our systems.

##### Children Under Age 13

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register with us or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@BicycleBlueBook.com](mailto:support@BicycleBlueBook.com).

##### Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18

We require that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

##### Limited Disclosure Situations

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through our service or using our name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents, or government agencies.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business, or individual business units owned by us were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made herein.

##### Links To Third Party Sites

Our web site may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on such site.

##### Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our web site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies which are inconsistent.

##### Questions

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact us at [support@BicycleBlueBook.com](mailto:support@BicycleBlueBook.com).
